hdmovieplus.com 2018-08-14

# Privacy Policy | HDMoviePlus

This Privacy Policy describes how HDMoviePlus ( “we,” “our” or “us”) collects, uses, and shares information about you and applies to your use of our websites, online services as well as all features, content, and other services that we own, control, and make available through our program(s) (collectively, the “Services”).

By using the Services, you agree to our collection, use, and disclosure practices, and other activities as described in this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service. If you do not agree, discontinue use of the Services. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at support@hdmovieplus.com.

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

### Contact forms

### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

### Analytics

We use Google Analytic.

## Who we share your data with

We do not share any personal data with anyone.

## How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

## What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

## Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

## Additional information

**Privacy Policy-** We never sell your personal information to third parties.  
We may use your IP address to help diagnose any problem with our service and to provide better services for our visitors.  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. The ads may contain cookies which may be used by the advertising companies to better understand a visitor’s preferences and help them to display related ads. However, the cookies received with the advertisements are collected by the advertising company and we do not have access to that information.These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.  
Email Addresses – We never share your email addresses with anyone.  
Log Files – As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (airtel, bsnl, mtnl, tata etc…), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.  
Cookies and Web Beacons – We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and would like to know your options in relation to not having this information used by these companies.  
We can be reached via our contact e-mail to **support@hdmovieplus.com**

— And —

Visitor Visit the Our Site and Free Download File to Third-Party’s Download Servers Example is :-  
1\. UsersCloud  
2\. IndiShare  
3\. 9xUpload  
4\. BDupload  
5\. Desiupload  
6\. Openload  
7\. Upgrand  
8\. ClicknUpload etc.  
Contact Us: **support@hdmovieplus.com**     [OR]    **plushdmovie@gmail.com**

(Get your email response within 2-3 days)
